

Nelson Ndukwe

Nationality: Nigerian (Nigeria) (+234) 9064035138 **Date of birth:** 28/07/2000

Gender: Male **Email address:** Nelsonndukwe800@gmail.com

Whatsapp Messenger: https://wa.me/+2349064035138

▼ Twitter: https://twitter.com/NelsonNdukwe6

(o) Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/nelsonndukwe/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/mwlite/in/nelson-ndukwe-040b6a168

• Address: 65 Hospital Road Aba, Abia State, Aba (Nigeria)

ABOUT ME

Result tasty individual with a track record of managing a community of international students on the Steemit blockchain. Experienced in managing front-end web architecture, the responsiveness of applications, and coordinating with user interface designers to bring live their designs. Conceptualizing, developing, testing, and implementing back-end front-end applications. Proficient in the use of Back-end languages such as Javascript, HTML, and CSS including other languages, and frameworks such as Node Js, React Js, and Express Js.

Founder and CEO of CampusConnect, a social interaction community built on the Steemit blockchain positioned to help students to interact, share campus-related experiences, and ultimately impact the world through sensational writing skills.

Ability to work under pressure, good communication skills, ability to learn quickly, and adapt to changing needs, good problem-solving skills, ability to work remotely, and crush deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Oak Capital [11/2021 - 03/2022]

Country: Nigeria

- Developed codes to complete assigned projects before deadline targets.
- Wrote, and modified existing packages/modules to assist in completing assigned projects.
- Completed projects using Node JS, React JS, HTML, CSS etc.
- Consumed external, and third-party restful APIs.
- Integrated APIs to correspond to design layouts.

Flutter Developer

NCK Technologies [01/2021 - 11/2021]

Country: Nigeria

- Wrote, modified, and debugged software for clients.
- Developed code to complete assigned projects by the deadline.
- Wrote, and modified existing packages/modules to assist complete assigned projects.
- I completed most projects using Dart, Flutter, Firebase, MongoDB, etc.
- Consumed external and third-party restful APIs.
- Designed some of the UI/UX mock-ups for development using Figma design tools.
- Integrated the APIs to correspond to the design layout

Web Developer

Complustech Ltd [07/2019 – 10/2019]

Country: Nigeria

- Develop, implement and keep track of digitally accessible information based on the information provided by the company.
- Align the company's goals with its digital footprint and presence.
- Develop clean. well-tested and excellent javascript code.
- Worked in different client environments, and settings as I accomplished my duties.
- Collaborated with technologists, and project managers to fulfill the scopes of each project.

Blockchain Blogger

Steemit Blockchain [2017 - Current]

Country: Nigeria

- Upload technical articles on the blockchain while using front-end languages to justify the articles.
- Manage the blockchain community I founded by implementing leadership skills.
- Build interpersonal skills which foster teamwork between other developers, and I on the blockchain.

Full Stack Developer

Real Desire Communications [2022 - 2022]

Country: Nigeria

- Systematically build a responsive website to process the transactions at the company which includes sorting, carting, and ordering.
- Use best coding practices to project the company's objectives and brand identity.
- Carried out de-bugging operations while optimizing, and fine-tuning

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering

Micheal Okpara University of Agriculture [2019 - 2024]

Address: Umuahia (Nigeria)

Python Development Bootcamp

Udemy [2022]

Address: (Nigeria)

Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy [2021]

Address: (Nigeria)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): English Language

Other language(s): Igbo Languages

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

React JS / HTML5/CSS, Javascript / Node JS / Express JS / Bootstrap / Relational Databases: SQL / SQL (MySql, SQLite, PostgreSQL, SQL Server) / Visual Studio Visual Basic